/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data9_2', {
    title: '9.2 Find the LCM',
    path: '9.2-find-the-lcm',
    children: [{
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{4}}}',
                answer: '\\input{4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 2 and 4.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{2}{4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{6}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}',
                answer: '\\input{6}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 6 and 2.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{6}{2}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{8}}}',
                answer: '\\input{8}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 4 and 8.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{4}{8}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{9}}}',
                answer: '\\input{18}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 6 and 9.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{6}{9}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{12}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{18}}}',
                answer: '\\input{36}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 12 and 18.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{12}{18}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{10}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{15}}}',
                answer: '\\input{30}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 10 and 15.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{10}{15}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}{\\str{ , }}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{8}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}',
                answer: '\\input{24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 4, 8, and 6.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{4}{8}{6}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{6}}}{\\str{ , }}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{15}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}',
                answer: '\\input{30}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 6, 15, and 5.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{6}{15}{5}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{24}}}{\\str{ , }}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{6}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{18}}',
                answer: '\\input{72}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 24, 6, and 18.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{24}{6}{18}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Find the LCM',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\str{Find the LCM of }}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{15}}}{\\str{ , }}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{18}}}{\\str{ and }}{\\frac{\\str{9}}{\\str{9}}',
                answer: '\\input{90}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Find the LCM of 15, 18, and 9.}',
                answer: '\\findlcm{15}{18}{9}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
